Finding Aid for Wilson Family Papers
William L. Clements Library, University of Michigan
- Wilson, William H.
  - Account Book, 1868 June 1-September 30 (Box 48)
1:23, 32, 33
2:26
8:80
43:33, 34
47:17
Livingston Manor (N.Y.)
11:80, 82, 88
12:99
Livingston, Robert R., 1746-1813
9:78, 82, 84, 85, 86, 89, 91, 92, 95, 98, 99
10:8, 9, 19, 28, 58, 64
11:15
12:13, 23, 92
Local government--New York (State)
See also Clermont (N.Y.)
4:20
Lotteries
1:79
3:15
Louisiana Purchase
12:23
Manufactures
16:2, 3
21:82
22:43
Medical care
5:38, 54, 69
7:6, 72
8:12, 45
11:29
12:33, 52
15:9, 18
16:88
27:45
36:19
42:4
Medical Society of Columbia County
15:69
Medicine
1:50
2:51, 56, 61
3:16, 68, 73, 85, 93, 94
4:43
5:61
14:48, 65, 69
17:21, 67
24:31
32:26, 44
35:61
47:10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16
Medicine--Study and teaching
See also New York Medical College
8:47
2:36, 53
5:56, 68
16:54, 64, 72, 76, 85
17:4, 15
Mexican War, 1846-1848
37:26, 52, 53, 62, 67
Middletown (Conn.)--Description and travel
1:18
Money
21:57
26:78
32:40
Monroe, James, 1758-1831
11:69
22:53
25:11
Mortgages
45:17
Napoleon I, Emperor of the French, 1769-1821
2:4
Napoleonic Wars, 1800-1815
18:14
20:29, 64
Nativism
15:16
Naval education
21:77
Neversink Turnpike Road Co.
41:14
New Orleans (La.)--Description and travel
28:74
New York & Erie Railroad
38:21
New York (N.Y.)--Description and travel
7:19
17:65
19:62
26:80
46:9
New York (N.Y.)--Economic conditions
30:53
35:56
38:77
New York (State)--Commerce
1:5
6:4
8:23
16:75
New York (State)--Description and travel
46:9
New York (State)--Economic conditions
7:63
20:67
36:3
New York (State)--Surveys
1:22, 43, 48, 49
3:38, 39, 86, 91
5:45, 62
6:69, 79, 108
7:8, 14, 25, 30
14:28, 64
46:8
New York (State). Constitution
27:37, 54
New York (State). Militia
38:42
New York Medical College
16:17, 44, 46, 52, 66
17:3, 23
45:18
New York State Medical Society
16:24, 44, 63, 70, 76, 80
17:13, 17, 29
45:19
Nicarauga
38:42
Nicoll family
42:11
Notaries
28:85
31:68
Paternity suits
See Illegitimacy
Philadelphia (Pa.)--Description and travel
30:80
Politics, Practical
3:57
4:27, 58, 73
5:15
6:6, 21, 81, 87, 90
7:83, 87, 88
8:17, 27, 75
9:92, 100
10:47, 48, 52, 53
11:37, 53, 59, 69, 89
12:12, 13, 14, 23, 89, 95
13:8, 9, 10, 11, 13, 59
14:11, 61, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 78, 81
15:19, 20, 28, 29, 30, 33, 34, 39, 43
16:4, 6, 73, 74, 77, 79, 85
17:33, 34, 35, 36, 41, 42, 46, 48, 50, 53
18:27
19:15, 66
20:9, 31
21:16, 34
22:16, 17, 18, 20, 21, 23, 24
23:57, 77
24:82, 83, 90, 96, 99, 100
25:72, 74, 80, 84, 86
26:48, 74, 89, 96, 102
28:67, 83
29:19, 20, 21, 22, 24, 65, 74
30:74
31:28, 33
32:28, 69, 74
34:14, 52
35:21, 24, 37
36:3, 27, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 40, 47
37:71, 73
38:4, 8, 39, 69, 70, 92
39:9
Postal service
1:46
2:8
4:79
12:72
23:50
24:69
26:30, 80
30:4
39:48, 49
42:14
Postal service--Accounting
42:12, 13
Power of attorney
43:45
Prices--New York (State)
2:29
3:20, 85
8:20, 30
9:31, 32, 34, 37, 38
10:49, 61
12:26
15:43
16:25
17:7, 44
18:19, 36
19:41, 42
20:19, 25, 39
25:87
26:92
27:8, 42
37:56
Prisons
14:41
Promissory notes
9:32
43:35
Public officers
28:85
31:68
Railroads
33:45
Real property--New York (State)
1:37, 55, 63, 65
2:9, 22, 27, 30, 64
3:3, 5, 50
Redhook (N.Y.)--Description and travel
31:66
Rent--New York (State)
1:53, 72
2:74
3:1, 11, 17, 35, 43
4:1, 24, 26, 52, 63, 64
5:55, 65
6:9, 19, 39, 47
7:9, 21
9:8
14:4, 52, 84
15:74
40:4
46:4, 7
Rent--New York (State)--Livingston Manor
46:3-6
Roads--New York (State)
10:4, 38
11:64
12:98
13:22
15:24
16:20
17:22
18:12
19:69
23:45
25:59, 83
26:3
29:20, 21
31:60
34:51, 54
41:3, 14
43:1, 2
Saint Andrews Society
23:26
Sanders family
42:11
Scarlatina
11:55, 57
24:94
Schools--New York (State)
9:2, 10, 13, 21, 24, 51
14:12, 13, 15
38:66
46:10
Schools--New York (State)--Clermont
41:22
Seminole War, 2nd, 1835-1842
24:87
Sharon (Conn.)--Description and travel
30:62
Sheep
10:58
11:15
13:62
16:14, 16, 25, 33, 48, 69, 71
17:7, 10, 12, 76, 77, 87
18:34, 58, 59
19:1, 20, 24, 28, 29, 33, 35, 53
20:20, 24, 27, 31, 35, 59, 71, 82, 91, 92
21:33, 42, 74, 78
24:36, 52, 54, 68, 75, 80
25:66
28:77
29:41, 42, 46, 50, 51, 63, 65, 79, 80
30:40, 43, 51, 86
32:70, 71, 72
Silverware
38:59
Slavery
1:17, 30, 35, 74
2:21, 93
4:55
9:10
10:36
11:17, 73
12:66
15:38
16:55
17:80
18:33, 35
19:33
24:24, 74
29:72
30:48
42:4
Smallpox
2:56
3:10
21:6
Spain--Description and travel
25:79
Sparkling wines--New York (State)--Clermont
35:41, 51
37:78
38:62
39:76
Squatters
1:52
3:8, 34, 40, 41, 62, 70, 78, 80, 86
4:14
15:62
Steamboats--New York (State)
7:48
17:70
19:30
22:48
26:87
33:40
Subpoena
43:46
Tariff
32:50
36:31
Taverns (Inns)--New York (State)--Clermont
21:23
Taxation--Carriage
19:6, 12
Taxation--Iowa--Adair County
46:9
Taxation--New York (State)
5:1
11:60
19:6, 12
46:9
Taxation--New York (State)--Clermont
46:9
Ten Broeck family
42:11
Timber
3:76
4:97
6:17, 32
7:58
11:22, 24, 49
12:15, 27, 74
14:10
16:12
23:22
26:8
29:78, 80, 82, 83, 84, 85
Transportation
12:28
Trespass
See also Timber
26:24
Union College
7:24
8:9, 16, 35, 41, 46, 51, 53
9:3
14:88
15:2, 40, 52, 53
United States--History--Revolution, 1775-1783
24:4
United States--History--1797-1801
2:4, 77
United States--History--War of 1812
17:8, 31, 38, 44, 45, 71
18:42, 43, 52
19:18, 26, 36, 47, 56, 57, 58, 60, 62
20:14, 15, 16, 18, 67
United States. Constitution
1:26
United States. Navy
14:56
21:72
22:31
25:65
37:51
Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862
25:72
Victoria, queen of Great Britain, 1819-1901
26:25
36:29
Wages
14:30
War
4:92
Warrants (Law)--New York (State)
41:17
Washington (D.C.)--Description and travel
30:80
Washington, George, 1732-1799
3:5, 13
7:64
Weather
8:26, 89
14:60
29:16, 75
30:30, 34
31:48
Wilson family
33:30, 46
42:11
Wool
20:44, 46, 49, 63
21:33, 63
22:20, 29
23:45
25:10
26:7, 14, 95
27:23, 24
28:68, 70
29:39
30:20, 21, 27, 30, 32, 34, 49, 72, 80
31:21, 22, 36, 40
32:5, 7, 8, 59
33:58
34:25, 26, 51
Yale College
16:62
Yellow fever
7:19, 35, 36
8:43
9:69, 71, 92, 98
24:97
28:17, 74
List of accounts and law cases
Merchants--Accounting
Abbott, William 44:1
Adams, John 44:1
Adee, David 44:1
Ainsley, Elias 44:1
Albany Argus 44:1
Albion 44:1
Alexander, J.R. 44:1
Alling, Samuel 44:1
Allyn, Joseph 44:1
American 44:1
American Express 44:1
American Union 44:1
Ames, Charles F. 44:1
Andrews, Ashbel 44:1
Andrews, Loring 44:1
Andrews and Woodruff 44:1
Andrum, James 44:1
Ann Street Church 44:1
Archer and Martin 44:1
Arcularius, P. G. 44:1
Armitage and Witts 44:1
Arnoux, Anthony 44:1
Arnoux, A. and G. A. 44:1
Arthur, Samuel 44:1
The Aurora 44:1
Austin, Charles 44:1
Austin and Andrews 44:1
Ayer, N. W. 44:1
Ayers, William 44:1
Bachman, Allen 44:2
Bachman, Allen 44:2
Backus and Whiting 44:2
Bacon, Edward 44:2
Bailey, James
John T. 44:2
Bailey and Holmes 44:2
Baker, A. W.
Henry
William A. 44:2
Bakewell, Thomas 44:2
Baldwin, Joseph 44:2
Baldwin and Cook 44:2
Ballard, G. 44:2
Bame, Jeremiah 44:2
Bank of Columbia 44:2
Bank of Hudson 44:2
Banker and Van Tilden 44:2
Banks, M. 44:2
Barber, John 44:2
Bardin, Edward 44:2
Barker and McCindrell 44:2
Barnes, P. 44:2
Barney, Margaret 44:2
Barnum, Charles P. 44:2
Barringer, R. 44:2
Barrington, R. 44:2
Bartholomew, Andrew 44:2
Barton, E. 44:2
Bassett, Joshua 44:2
Bayard, Stephen N. 44:2
Becker, Peter 44:2
The Bee 44:2
Beekman, John 44:2
Bell, Isabella
John 44:3
Bement, George 44:3
Ben 44:3
Bender, Henry 44:3
Bennett, Henry 44:3
Benton, Samuel
Thomas
William 44:3
Bernet 44:3
Bessar, H. W. 44:3
Best, George C.
Jacob
John 44:3
Bigelow andd Isham 44:3
Bininger, A. 44:3
Blain, James 44:3
Blass, John
Philip 44:3
Blatner, Marks 44:3
Bleeker, James 44:3
Blew, Moses 44:3
Bloodgood, James G.
Thomas 44:3
Bogardus, James
Samuel 44:3
Bogardus and Groat 44:3
Bolles, John 44:3
Bonesteel, Henry
Jacob N. 44:4
Bonesteel and Broadhead
Bonesteel and Foland
Bonesteel and Wachaugen 44:4
Bostwick, C. B.
R. W. 44:5
Bourne, Mary 44:5
Bowman, N. 44:5
Bradstreet, Andrew 44:5
Brand, H. Little 44:5
Brau, James 44:5
Brett and Bunn 44:5
Breuster, H. and S. 44:5
Brink, Andrew 44:5
Broadwell, William 44:5
Bronk, Richard 44:5
Brooksbank, William 44:5
Brown, E. M.
Jedediah
Thomas 44:5
Browning, Jeremiah
Robert 44:5
Bruce, William and Robert 44:5
Bruce and Morrison 44:5
Buel, Jesse 44:5
Bunker, William J. 44:5
Bunker and Van Siclen 44:5
Burchsted and Barnard 44:5
Burhans, Isaac 44:5
Burk, James 44:5
Burwell, Calvin 44:5
Butler, Erastus 44:5
Cadiness, John K. 44:6
Caldwell, James and Son 44:6
Campbell, Samuel 44:6
Cantine, Peter 44:6
Cantine and Meyer
Cantine, Van Ness and Heermance 44:6
Capron, A.
Cyrus
William P. 44:6
Cargill, Abraham 44:6
Carpenter, A. 44:6
Carr, William 44:6
Carrique, P. Dean 44:6
Carswell and Eaton 44:6
Carvill, G. and C.
G. C. and H. 44:6
Cauldwell, Ebenezer 44:6
Champlin 44:6
Chandler, Solomon 44:6
Chase, G.
Mary H. 44:6
Cholwell, J. 44:6
Christie, T. and J. 44:6
Church Journal 44:6
Churchman and Parson 44:6
City-Hall Register 44:6
Clark and Baldwin
Clark and Bawlding
Clark and Horsford
Clark and Tallmadge 44:6
Clow, Henry 44:6
Clum, Henry P. 44:6
Cockburn, James 44:7
Cockburn, J. and G. Miller 44:7
Coffin, Robert 44:7
Cogswell, J. and M. 44:7
Cole, Peter B. 44:7
Collins, Nathan
Peter B. 44:7
Columbia Hall 44:7
Columbia County Mutual Insurance Co. 44:7
Columbian 44:7
Commercial Advertizer 44:7
Comstock, Ebenezer 44:7
Congress (Steamboat) 44:7
Conklin, J. 44:7
Cook, Palmer 44:7
Cook and Baker 44:7
Coon, Alex
Philip W. 44:7
Cooper, Elisabeth
Jacob
John
Peter F.
Thomas 44:7
Cooper and Bogardus 44:7
Corry, Samuel 44:7
Coster, J. 44:7
Cotheal and Huff 44:7
Country Post 44:7
Cox, John 44:7
Crapner, Alfred 44:7
Crary, E. R. 44:7
Crawford, George 44:7
Crawford and Trumphorn 44:7
Creiger, John L. 44:7
Crook and Fowks
Crook and Ten Broeck 44:7
Crosswell, E. 44:7
Cultivator and Register 44:7
Cummings, James 44:7
Currie, Archibald and David 44:7
Curtis, C.
Seth 44:7
Daily Times 44:8
Darling, Charles A. 44:8
Darling and Power 44:8
Daily Tribune 44:8
Davis, Ann
David
Henry
Jabez
Jacob
John G.
William 44:8
Day, John 44:8
Dean and Storm 44:8
Deane, William 44:8
Decker, Peter
Richard 44:8
DeHart, Cyrus 44:8
DeLameter, G. E. 44:8
DeLameter and heermance 44:8
Deneger, Albert
Ephraim
George
Jonas 44:8
Denty, M. 44:8
DePeyster, F. 44:8
Devereaux, E. 44:8
DeWitt, Henry 44:8
Dey, Anthony 44:8
Dibblee, Fyler
Henry
H. F.
Richard H. 44:9
Dibblee, Bostwick and Co. 44:9
Dick, J. 44:9
Dickson and Manny 44:9
Dimmick, Thomas 44:9
Dodge, William 44:9
Donnelly, John 44:9
Dorning, A. I. 44:9
Doty, James 44:9
Doyle, Louis 44:9
Drum, Matthias 44:9
Drummond, James P. 44:9
Duane Street Church 44:9
DuBois and Voorhis 44:9
Duncan, Cato 44:9
Dunderdale, J. and F. 44:9
Dunkan, L. and W. 44:9
Dunlop and Wilson 44:9
Dunspaugh, Henry 44:9
Dutcher, John W. 44:9
Dutchess Democrat 44:9
Duychinck, Gerrardus Jr. 44:9
Dykers, Alstyne and Co. 44:9
Eaton and Lasher 44:10
Eclectic Magazine 44:10
Eliot, Nathan 44:10
Ellsworth, Henry 44:10
Elting, J. Jr.
H. and R.
Robert 44:10
Elting and Co
Elting and Varrick 44:10
Elton, Cyprian
Rhesa 44:10
Ely, R. 44:10
Ely & Nuttman 44:10
Emmett & White 44:10
Eustis, F. A. 44:10
Evans & Brown 44:10
Evening Post 44:10
Feary, John 44:10
Feller, George
Philip 44:10
Feller & Robinson 44:10
Fields, Peter 44:10
Finck, W. B. 44:10
Finck and Capron 44:10
Finkel, John 44:10
Fish, Henry 44:10
Fitch, Hendrick 44:10
Flagler, Joseph 44:10
Fletcher, Joseph 44:10
Fletcher and Scuddle 44:10
Foland, William 44:10
Folger, Rueben 44:10
Forbus, John 44:10
Fraleigh, John P. 44:10
Fryer and VanVliet 44:10
Funk, William 44:10
Fulmes, Anthony 44:10
Gage, Hiram 44:11
Gale, Ira
Jeremiah 44:11
Gale and Barringer 44:11
Gardner, G.
Joshua
Richard 44:11
Gardner & Drayton 44:11
Gaul, J. & D. 44:11
Gazette of the United States 44:11
Gerry, J. & W. 44:11
Gelston, Cotton 44:11
General Protestant Episcopal Sunday School Union and Church Book Society 44:11
Gibbs, William 44:11
Gibson, James
William 44:11
Gifford, A.
E. 44:11
Gilbert, Ashley 44:11
Gill, John M.
Robert 44:11
Godey's Lady's Book 44:11
Gojon, Claudius F. 44:11
Gould, E. P.
Stephen 44:11
Gould and Banks 44:11
Gracie and Co. 44:11
Graham, William 44:11
Green, Ann
Samuel 44:11
Greenleaf, Thomas 44:11
Gridley, O. 44:11
Grier, John 44:11
Grier, J., Brooks and Co. 44:11
Haight, Benjamin
John and Nicholas
Samuel 44:12
Hall, Aaron C.
A. C.
H. C. 44:12
Hall, Fuller, and Barlowe 44:12
Hallock and Shelden 44:12
Halsted, O. 44:12
Ham, Jeremiah
Peter C. 44:12
Hamersley, Thomas 44:12
Hamlin, David
G. 44:12
Hamlin, Dibblee and Col. 44:12
Hannah, William 44:12
Hardenburgh, Johannes 44:12
Harvey, John 44:12
Hassman, John B.
P. 44:12
Hathaway, John
S. S. 44:12
Hatten, James 44:12
Hattrick, Mary Lee 44:12
Haner, Samuel 44:12
Hawley, E.
George 44:12
Heenberg, J. P. 44:13
Heermance, Andrew
Martin 44:13
Henry, William 44:13
Herbert, John L. 44:13
Herrick, S. H. 44:13
Hicks, Elias 44:13
Hicks and Merrick 44:13
Hill, R. H. 44:13
Hillicker, Norman 44:13
Hitchcock, Miles 44:13
Hoffman, A. N.
D. D.
Herman
Mrs.
Zacharius 44:13
Hoffman and Sons
Hoffman and Van Buren
Hoffman, Van Deusen and Co. 44:13
Holbrook, Eliot 44:14
Holley, E. C. 44:14
Holt, Charles 44:14
Hopkins, George F. 44:14Irvin, Adam 44:14
Israel, William 44:14
Jackson, Robert 44:15
Janson, John B. 44:15
Jarvis, Bulkley, and Wheeler 44:15
Jenkins, Elisha
James
Robert
Thomas 44:15
Jenings, S. C. 44:15
John, H. and Ogle 44:15
Johnson, John P.
William 44:15
Johnston, John C. 44:15
Jones, William R. 44:15
Jones and Clinch 44:15
Journeay, James 44:15
Kelly, James 44:15
Kemper, John 44:15
Kenney, John 44:15
Ketchum, Joseph 44:15
Kiersted, Luke 44:15
King, George
Joseph
Vincent
William O. 44:15
King & McGill 44:15
Kingoland, Richard 44:15
Kingston Academy 44:15
Kirby & Yeats 44:15
Kiss, Luke 44:15
Knickerbocker, Edwin
Philip 44:15
Knickerbocker and Washburn 44:15
Kortz, John 44:15
Labagh, John T. 44:16
Lamb, George C. 44:16
Lambert, James 44:16
Lane, James
Jonathan
R. and A. 44:16
Lansing, Turner & Co. 44:16
Lasher, B. C.
Bostian
Elias
George B.
George C.
John G. Jr.
John L.
P. N.
Rufus 44:16
Lasher and Shook 44:16
Latham, James 44:16
Lawrence, James
Joseph 44:16
Leander 44:16
LeBreton, Edward A. 44:16
Lee, James
Mary 44:16
LeRoy, Levi
Theodore 44:16
Lescure, H. 44:16
Lewis, Morgan
Thomas 44:16
Littbertson, Morris 44:17
Littell, E. 44:17
Living Age 44:17
Livingston, Crawford
Edward P.
Henry
M. and C.
Margaret
Peter R.
Robert
Robert R.
W. T. and J. C.
William A. 44:17
Lodi Manufacturing Co. 44:17
Loscher, Conrad 44:17
Losee, Cyrus 44:17
Lounds, Oliver M. 44:17
Lovering, J. And S. 44:17
Ludlow, Julian 44:17
Luff, N. W. and Co. 44:17
Luffman, John 44:17
Lynch and Dibbles 44:17
Lynk 44:17
MacArthur, C. 45:1
McCaskey, John 45:1
McCrindell, James and Thomas 45:1
McDougall, Peter M. 45:1
McGill, William 45:1
McKinley, George 45:1
McKinstry and White 45:1
McLean 45:1
McManus, M. P. 45:1
MacNicol, Alexander 45:1
Macy and Hors 45:1
Mancius, George W. 45:1
Mandeville, William 45:12
Mansfield, James L. 45:1
Mansfield and Smith
Mansfield and Shirtz 45:1
Mansion House 45:1
Marchall, Milo 45:1
Marquand, F. 45:1
Martin, Edward 45:1
Martin and Myers 45:1
Masier, Eli 45:1
Masier and Bennett 45:1
Mate, J. 45:1
Medical Repository 45:1
Merfield, Walter 45:1
Mennemy, Robert M. 45:1
Merchants Canal / Transportation Line 45:1
Merrick, Justin 45:1
Merry's Museum45:1
Mesier, P. A. 45:1
Mesler and Ballard 45:1
Methuen, James 45:1
Meyer, G. and T.
John 45:1
Midler, Christopher 45:2
Miller, Peter 45:2
Miller and Feller
Miller and Gaul
Miller and Punderson 45:2
Mills, John 45:2
Miner, Elisha
Eunice
Erastus 45:2
Mink, Henry
Philip H. 45:2
Minkler, Adam
Jacob
Kilian 45:2
Mitchell, Charles 45:2
Mitchell, Mr's Church 45:2
Moffett, H. 45:2
Moore, Benjamin
Conrad
John
John, Jr.
Philip
Samuel 45:2
Moore and Robertson 45:2
Morange, B. and Son
James 45:2
Morgan, Hubbel 45:2
Morris, R. H. 45:2
Muldoon and Montgomery 45:2
Museum 45:2
Muller, Peter 45:2
Munson, John 45:2
Murch, Robert H. 45:2
Murray and Beyer 45:2
Nash, Samuel 45:2
National Advocate 45:4
National Democrat 45:4
National Hotel 45:4
Near, H. and L. 45:4
Nelson, Thomas and Son 45:4
New World 45:4
New York American 45:4
New York and Schuylkill Coal Co. 45:4
New York Daily Advertizer 45:4
New York Dry Dock Co. 45:4
New York Enquirer 45:4
New York Evening Post 45.4
New York Herald 45:4
New York Historical Collections 45:4
New York Statesman 45:4
New York Tribune 45:4
New Yorker 45:4
Newkirk, C. 45:4
Nexson, William E. 45:4
Nichols, David 45:4
Nichols and Wilcox 45:4
Nittebrants 45:4
Noah's Enquirer 45:4
Norman, Joseph P.
William E. 45:4
Northern Whig 45:4
Norton, John S. 45:4
Nortwick and Miller 45:4
Nova Scotia Coal Depot 45:4
Noyes, S. H. 45:4
Oakley, Daniel 45:5
O'Dell, Isaac 45:5
Opsley, R. and I. H. 45:5
Outwater, Peter 45:5
Owens, Jesse 45:5
Paddock, John 45:6
Palmer, William 45:6
Paine, Catherine 45:6
Panorama 45:6
Park, Jacob 45:6
Parker, Ransom 45:6
Parkman, Thomas 45:6
Parks, Mills 45:6
Parley's Magazine 45:6
Parsons, I. and C.
Jales 45:6
Patrie, N. 45:6
Patterson, Robert 45:6
Paulding, Nathaniel 45:6
Pease and Wiswall 45:6
Pellett, Joel 45:6
Penfold, John 45:6
Penn, Joshua 45:6
Penny Magazine 45:6
Perkins, James T. 45:6
Peters, A. S. 45:6
Phillips, George 45:6
Pierce, John 45:6
Platner, Freeman 45:6
Platt, Isaac
Israel 45:6
Platt and Co. 45:6
Pleasant Valley Boarding School 45:6
The Plough Boy 45:6
Plumb, Samuel 45:6
Porter, James
N.B. 45:6
Potter, P.
William P. 45:6
Potts, Henry
Peter
William H. 45:6
Potts and Moore 45:6
Power, Isaac
Nicholas
Thomas 45:6
Power and Livingston 45:6
Pratt, Erastus 45:6
Prober, David 45:6
Punderson, Ebenezer
F.
Gifford 45:6
Punderson and Van Valkenburg 45:6
Purdy, R. L. and G. W. Betts 45:6
Puree, Smith 45:6
Racy, Charles 45:7
Rathbone, J. 45:7
Rause, H. 45:7
Rawson, Stephen 45:7
Raynor and Ten Broeck 45:7
Redfield, Bernard 45:7
Reed, Rufus 45:7
Reed and Gage 45:7
Reid, Isaac 45:7
Republican Telegraph 45:7
Reynolds, Gamaliel
James S. 45:7
Richmond, John
L.
Thomas 45:7
Rider, George T. 45:7
Riely, F. 45:7
Riggs, William H. C. 45:7
Ripley, Charles 45:7
Rivers, Adam 45:7
Robertson, John 45:7
Robinson, John
Peter 45:7
Rockefeller, Peter
Robert 45:7
Rockefeller and Platner
Rockefeller and Sharp
Rockefeller and Simmons 45:7
Rodman, Thomas 45:7
Rogers, W. T. 45:7
Roive, Thomas 45:7
Roome, Jacob 45:8
Roorbach, Arthur H. 45:8
Roraback, Uriah 45:8
Rose and Hurley 45:8
Rossman and McKinstry 45:8
Row, Matthew 45:8
Row and Reed 45:8
Rowley, J. and D.
John
W. and D. 45:8
Rudder, Frederick 45:8
Russell, J. 45:8
Rutherford, Walter 45:8
Fyfenbergh, Alex
Peter 45:8
Ryker, John 45:8
Sagendorph, D.
George
H. L. 45:9
Sagendorph and Potts 45:9
St. Johns, Oliver R. 45:9
Salisbury, John 45:9
Saltback, Jacob
P. 45:9
Sanders, John 45:9
Schenck, Sarah 45:9
Schermerhorn, Betsey 45:9
Schmidt, Matthias 45:9
Schuyler and Myers 45:9
Scriba, Frederick
George 45:9
Scriba, Schoeppel, and Starman 45:9
Secor and Priest 45:9
Seelgraph, Jacob 45:9
Semi-Monthly Magazine 45:9
Semi-Weekly Tribune 45:9
Seymour and Macy 45:9
Sewall, H. D. and H. P. 45:9
Sharp, A. 45:9
Sharp and DuBois 45:9
Sharp, Granz and Co. 45:9
Shear, H. 45:9
Shepperd, R. T. 45:9
Shook, J. R. 45:9
Showers, John 45:
Shufeldt, M. 45:9
Shults, Peter 45:9
Simons, Titus 45:9
Sipperly, William 45:9
Skinner, H. D. 45:9
Smith, Charles
Eleazer
George B.
Gilbert
Giles
James L.
John P.
Lorentz
Michael
Samuel
T. Tredwell 45:9
Smith, Littlefield and West 45:9
Snyder, H.
Samuel 45:10
Southart, Jacob 45:10
Sparkman, James D. 45:10
Spencer, M. 45:10
Sperry, Jacob 45:10
Staats, J. P.
Peter
Widow 45:10
Stebbins, Francis
William B. 45:10
Steel, John B. 45:10
Stephen, Coffin, and Peckham 45:10
Stevens, J. H. 45:10
Steward, John 45:10
Stockholm and Browney 45:10
Stocking, A.
Samuel 45:10
Stoddard, Ashbel 45:10
Stokes, ____
H. and A. 45:10
Stone and Corss 45:10
Storm, Thomas 45:10
Storrs, A.
W. and G. 45:10
Story, Judge 45:10
Strong, Jeremiah
Joseph
Peter 45:10
Stuart, James 45:10
Suides 45:10
Swart, Cornelius
Thomas 45:10
Swartwout, John 45:10
Sword, T. and J. 45:10
Talmadge and Southerland 45:11
Tappen, Cornelius 45:11
Taylor, John
Philip H.
Robert 45:11
Teal, William H. 45:11
Teats, B. 45:11
Teller, James 45:11
Ten Broeck, Hudson
J. V. R.
Samuel 45:11
Ten Broeck and Benjamin 45:11
Thomas, Thomas 45:11
Thompson, Samuel 45:11
Thomson, Thomas 45:11
Throckmorton, William 45:11
Tobey, Silas 45:11
Tomes, Henry 45:11
Tooker, Martin
Samuel 45:11
Traver, John P. 45:11
Travis and Shook 45:11
Trempen, William 45:11
Turcot, Peter D. 45:11
Union College 45:11
Union Transportation Line 45:11
United States Fire Insurance Co. 45:11
Valkenburgh, Christian 45:12
Van Antwerp, P. 45:12
Van Beuren, Henry
Peter B. 45:12
Van Buren, P. 45:12
Van Buren and Clow
Van Buren and Livingston
Van Buren and Reed 45:12
Van De Bogart, R. V. 45:12
Vandenberg and Pendleton 45:12
Vandervoom, W. and P. L. 45:12
Van Deusen, John
David
H. B.
P.
Richard D. 45:12
Van Deusen and DuBois
Van Deusen and Gaul
Van Deusen and Reed 45:12
Van Dyke, Miss 45:12
Van Etten 45:13
Van Horn, James 45:13
Van Lewen, John 45:13
Van Loew, M. D. and B. 45:13
Van Ness, David and Son
G. B.
Jacob
45:13
Van Nortwick and Miller 45:13
Van Ranst, A. M. 45:13
Van Rensselaer, Henry R. 45:13
Van Schaack, John
Peter 45:13
Van Steenburgh, Jacob B. 45:13
Van Vleck, Abraham 45:13
Van Vleck and Cantine 45:13
Van Valkenburgh and Rossman 45:13
Varrick, Richard 45:13
Villee, Cornelius 45:13
Voris and Buckle 45:13
Vosburgh, Martin 45:13
Vravenburgh, William 45:13
Wachenhagen, Augustus
Mary 45:14
Waggoner, Peter W. 45:14
Waite, G. and R. 45:14
Waldo, D. R. 45:14
Waldo and Lower 45:14
Wall Street House 45:14
Walsh, J. O. 45:14
Walter, Henry 45:14
Warren, Aaron 45:14
Washburn, K. 45:14
Washburn and Moore 45:14
Watch Tower 45:14
Watson, L. Z.
M. J. 45:14
Watts, John 45:14
Wawley, E. and G. 45:14
Weaver, Adam A. 45:14
Week, Mrs. 45:14
Weekly Museum 45:14
Weeks, Peter 45:14
Welch, Jesse 45:14
Westchester (steamboat) 45:14
Wescott, Samuel 45:14
Westervelt and Munson 45:14
Westmore and Channing 45:14
Wey, Gurden 45:14
Wheeler 45:14
Whitaker, Joseph
O. 45:14
White, Ann
John
Philip
Samuel 45:14
Whitemarsh, Sameul and Co. 45:14
Whitney, S. 45:14
Wigman and Clark 45:15
Wilbur, H.
Solomon Jr. 45:15
Wilby, William 45:15
Wilcox, John 45:15
Willcox, Abner 45:15
Willetts, Doty, and Co. 45:15
Williams, William 45:15
Wilson, A. W.
Hannah S.
Robert L.
R. and W.
William
William H. 45:15
Wilson and Dibblee 45:15
Winteringham, David
Sidney 45:16
Wiswall and Jenkins 45:16
Wolcott, C. C. 45:16
Wood, David
James
Timothy 45:16
Woodworth, A. 45:16
Wyckoff, Samuel 45:16
Wynkoop, Arritha
Cornelius 45:16
Yeo, S.
45:16
Young, Henry
J. and S.
John 45:16
Young People's Book
45:16
Younglove and West
45:16
Law—Cases [N.B.: Both plaintiffs and defendants are included, intermixed, in the following listing, without reference to a role in a particular case.]
Babcock, William 43:8
Backer, William 43:22
Bacon, Converse 43:23
Bandoline and Chapman 43:22
Bank, Franklin 43:5
Bartlett, Robert 43:6
Bay, John 43:23
Becker, William 43:22
Benedict, James 43:7
Benjamin [slave] 43:23
Benson, Matthew 43:22
Bentley, William N. 43:23
Bogert, John G. 43:22
Brasher 43:20
Broadhead, Thomas 43:23
Brown 43:23
Brown, John C. 43:8
Brown, Stephen G. 43:22
Brown, Thomas 43:22
Burras, Jane 43:22
Byron, Harriet 43:22
Byron, Willimina 43:22
Cantello, William J. 43:17
Capron, Cyrus 43:23
Cheetham, James 43:22
Clermont. [NY] 43:23
Cock, Townsend 43:10
Columbia County. NY 43:23
Conant, Samuel 43:23
Conklin, Joel 43:10
Corbin, Francis 43:10
Corry, Samuel 43:11
Cox and Duffy 43:22
Crawbuck, Peter 43:23
Crookshank, Grace 43:23
Crysler, Mattys 43:22
DeLameter, [Peter?] 43:23
Deming, Lemuel 43:12
Dewey, Timothy 43:23
Dodd, Moses 43:22
Duane, Mrs. 43:22
Dubois, Cornelius 43:22
Duyer, Antonia and William 43:23
Edwards, George C. 43:23
Elmendorph, Edmund 43:15
Elsworth, John 43:22, 23
Fris, Jacob 43:22
George, Hannah 43:22
Goest, Lucas 43:22
Gould, Stephen 43:5
Gould, William 43:22
Granger, [N.Y.] 43:23
Gwyer, Charles 43:23
Haircott, John 43:22
Hall, Abraham (estate) 43:22
Hall, Henry 43:13
Hamlin, Asher P. 43:14
Harrison, James 43:23